Viewers all over the world, whatever medium you are using to watch us, just believe.
Hallelujah!
Our human eyes can be blind to His act of mercy, to His act of healing, deliverance and salvation.
Lift up your voice and ask Jesus to restore your sight
so that you can feel His touch and hear Him say that you are healed.
And hear Him say that you are blessed, you are free. Lift up your voice. Oh Lord Jesus, restore my sight.
My human eyes can be blind to Your act of mercy, to Your act of blessing.
Oh Lord Jesus, restore my sight and let me feel Your touch.
Prayer.
Viewers all over the world, open your lips.
Your human eyes can be blind to His act of mercy,
to His act of blessing, to His act of salvation.
Lift up your voice and ask the Lord to restore your sight, so that you can feel His touch.
So that you will hear Him say: "You are healed; you are blessed."
Open your lips. Restore my sight, Lord.
Restore my sight, Lord, to feel Your touch and hear You say that we are delivered.
Open your lips!
Restore my sight, Lord.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Let someone say: "Let me feel His touch."
I can't hear you.
Let me feel His touch!
Yes. Let me feel His touch and hear Him say: "I am healed, I am delivered, I am saved."
Somebody touched me
Somebody touched my soul
When I was praying, praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul.
Let me feel His touch!
Let someone say.
I can't hear you.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord!
Again and again.
I can't hear you.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord - touch of salvation.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord - touch of blessing.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord - touch of healing.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord - touch of breakthrough.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord - touch of freedom.
Let me feel Your touch, Lord!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
He is Lord. Amen. He has risen from the dead and He is Lord
Every knee shall bow every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord
While waiting for deliverance, begin to rejoice in your heart.
Say: "I am delivered."
While waiting for deliverance, say: "I am delivered."
Begin to act faith right before that.
While waiting for deliverance, act faith. I am delivered in Jesus' name.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
While waiting for deliverance, begin to act faith.
I am delivered, Jesus is my Deliverer. In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Viewers, while waiting for deliverance, right now begin to confess:
"I am delivered, Jesus is my Deliverer."
While waiting for deliverance. I am delivered; Jesus is my Deliverer.
Confess. Begin to act faith.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Begin to act faith right now, act faith. While waiting for deliverance.
While waiting for deliverance - I am delivered, Jesus is my Deliverer.
Overflow Congregation
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
If the Son sets you free, you are free indeed. Be delivered, in Jesus' name.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Every spirit that challenges you!
Every spirit that challenges your career.
Every spirit that challenges your marriage.
Every spirit that challenges your family.
Every spirit that challenges your journey.
Every spirit that challenges your business, your career.
Out!
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I stretch my right hand to talk to your spirit, to release your spirit from every spirit.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Agree with me - I am going to release my spirit.
In the name of Jesus.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You satan, loose your grip.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers, every spirit that stands against you, every spirit that challenges you,
every spirit that challenges your career,
every spirit that stands against you, stands against your business -
loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Leave my people.
You demon, leave my people.
Leave their career. I say, leave my people.
Say: "I am a child of God. I say - no! You satan, no!"
I'm a child of God! No!
Whatever contact, I'm a child of God - no! Be it your business, be it your career, be it your marriage
be it your marriage, be it your future. Whatever contact, I'm a child of God - no!
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus.
I release you! Be released!
Whatever contact - be it your business, your career, your marriage, your family, your health -
whatever contact, say: "I am a child of God. I say - no!"
You satan, I say - no!
In the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Break it! Any contact - begin to break it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers, begin to break it, break any contact. Whatever contact.
You are a child of God. Take your dominion!
Take your dominion! Say - no! No!
Break whatever contact, break it.
Be it your business - break it, break it!
Be it your family - break it, break it!
Be it your career - break it, break it !
Your health - break it, break it! Prayer - begin to break it!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
Right now, take your dominion in Christ Jesus.
Move! Begin to break satan! Break whatever connection!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself, to connect your family, your marriage - break it!
Take your dominion in Christ Jesus. Begin to break it, in the name of Jesus!
I break it! I break whatever connection. Prayer!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus. Whatever satan might have taken, begin to receive it.
My business, my perfect business, my excellent business, career, my excellent career -
I take it, I take it! My excellent ministry. My business, my excellent business.
My career, my excellent career! My marriage, my excellent marriage -
take it - whatever satan might have taken from you.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In Jesus' name! I hear Jesus say: "You are delivered."
Listen. I can hear Jesus say - you are delivered.
Listen again. I hear Jesus say - you are delivered!
Whatever sickness, disease now
that would disturb this fine future the Lord has given to you, wherever the sickness is located -
in your blood, in your bone, in your kidney, in your liver - right now command it out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus.
That sickness in your blood - I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Whatever sickness, wherever it is located - out, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Talk to your organ, your system. Begin to talk to your organ. In the name of Jesus,
I send His Word to your organ.
Send God's Word to your organ.
Wherever you have that disease, that pain - send the Word.
Let the sick say: "I am healed." Send the Word.
Send the Word, wherever it is located.
You disease, you sickness, you infirmity! Speak out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Speak out! Speak out!
Wherever it is located!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Unknown place...
Wherever that disease is located, wherever that infirmity,
wherever that disease, infirmity - I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Hear the voice of God, you disease.
You infirmity, hear the voice of God.
Out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In your blood, in your kidney, in your liver, in your bone - say: "Out in the name of Jesus!"
Say: "Out! In the name of Jesus!"
Whatever sickness or disease you might have taken in your dreams, right now begin to flash it out.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Whatever poison you might have taken...
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In whatever way the disease, sickness might have entered your bone, your blood...
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Open your lips, rebuke it. Begin to rebuke it out!
Say - out! Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In Jesus Christ's name.
Agree with me - I'm healed; Jesus is my Healer.
I can't hear you!
I can see you being healed, in Jesus Christ's name!
I can't hear you. In Jesus Christ's name!
If there is anyone here that is struggling with her or his faith, I release you, in the name of Jesus.
You are there, you are struggling with your faith - "I believe, help my unbelief!"
Be released, in the name of Jesus! Be fit, in the name of Jesus!
You are struggling with your faith, your belief. Right now, be fit, in the name of Jesus.
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Have the right to believe. Faith is of God. Have the faith, in the name of Jesus!
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Viewers all over the world, begin to cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
I cover myself with the blood of Jesus.
Feel His touch, in the name of Jesus.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua. Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, your nation, your country - lift up your voice and pray for your country.
Prayer For The Nations With T.B. Joshua
Pray for your country - under His eyes. My nation - under His eyes.
God's intervention. In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Prayer For The Nations With T.B. Joshua
I can't hear your "amen".
Right now, those of us that are just coming to Christ for the first time and those of us who want to rededicate ourselves -
open your lips right now. Lord Jesus, wash me with Your precious blood.
Make me Your channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Make me Your channel of pardon where there is injury.
Make me Your channel of forgiveness where there is sin.
Make me Your channel of love where there is hatred, in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Thank you, Lord, for dying in my place. Thank you for your salvation. In Jesus Christ's name.
Let someone say: "Amen".
You can remain silent right now. And make your promise to Christ.
A promise still standing. Out there, they need a channel of shining light.
As you are leaving, you are God's channel of love where there is hate.
As you are leaving, you are God's channel of faithfulness where there is unfaithfulness.
As you are leaving, you are God's channel.
Say: "I am God's channel of shining light where there is darkness."
As you are leaving, you are God's channel of forgiveness where there is sin.
God's channel of pardon where there is injury.
These are the promises right now you want to make. Remain quiet and silent and make this promise.
As a channel of God out there. Wherever you are - channel of God.
In the East - channel of God. South - channel of God. North, West - channel of God.
Where there is crisis - channel of God. Where there is disobedience - channel of God.
Where there is hate - channel of God. So this is promise you have to make now before you leave.
I am standing to tell you that old things pass away; God has renewed you.
It is a new dawn to your business!
It is a new dawn to your family!
It is a new dawn to your career!
I mean, it is a new dawn to your health!
It is a new dawn to your marriage!
It is a new dawn to your family, to your business, to your finances, to your business partners, to your nation, country.
It is a new dawn. Good morning!
Greet your neighbor: "Good morning! It is a new dawn."
Good morning! It is a new dawn to your finances!
Good morning! It is a new dawn to your career!
Good morning! It is a new dawn! Indeed, it is a new dawn!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer.
TT Monica Asefa 11/07/18
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 28/37/2018